And “made up my mind,
“I'll ask for a threesome
(Howard:)and if they say no,
play it off as a joke.”
(Raj:)I'm calling her.
(Raj:)And the threesome didn't deserve
the belly laugh it got.
(Bernadette:)You're right.
(stifled laughter):
It could totally happen.
CLAIRE:
Hello?
(Raj:)Hi. Hi. Yeah, it's Raj.
(Raj:)Rajesh.
We met at the comic book store.
(Claire:)Hey, what's up? Figure out
what time you're free?
(Girl:)Actually,
that's why I'm calling.
(Raj:)I, um... I just...
(Raj:)I need to let you know
that I have a girlfriend.
(Claire:)Okay. Good for you.
(Raj:)Well, no, no.
I-I didn't want to mislead you
(Raj:)after you asked me out.
(Claire:)I didn't ask you out.
(Claire:)I just need help
with my screenplay.
(Raj:)Wait, are you saying
that we didn't have a vibe?
(Claire:)Why do you care if we have
a vibe? You have a girlfriend.
Come on! I just told you
I had a girlfriend.
(Raj:)The least you can do is tell me
if we had a vibe.
(Claire:)Sure, we had a vibe.
(Raj:)I knew it.
Okay, we did have a vibe.
(Raj:)This is exciting.
(Raj:)What's my next move?
(Bernadette:)You still have a girlfriend.
(Raj:)Right. Good catch.